welcome back
now that our journey is complete
I think we could have a nice recap of our adventure
our whole base is located in a single self sufficient dimension
here there is no rain
no mob spawn
and it's always day
we received this place as a reward when we built our first rocket
and this is the main hall of the building
in the middle of our base
here we have a screen
that will show us the charge of our main battery
some monitor terminals to keep an eye on the amount of fuel
and some for the endgame stuff
talking about storage and craftings
our main ae2 controller is right above us
to manage all of its channels in an easier way
we used a tight mix of peer to peer and wireless connectors
to get all of the controller facades on a nice wall
we can see all of the channels with our network visualizer
but that doesn't really help us that much while working in that location
here we also have all of our crafting CPUs
we have different sizes
but the biggest ones are those towers equipped with singularity crafting storages
those can hold crafting orders up to 8 exabytes
while we will never get close to that amount
they are helpful when doing huge orders
that would otherwise need too big conventional CPUs
all of those CPUs are also doing some crafting self started
those are not from crafting cards or level emitters
but from level maintainers
with those it is easy to keep a stock of what we want
and when needed, request a craft with a specific batch size
next to that we have our main generic storage
and to manage all of those items
we ended up using the artificial universe storage cells
but this is just our main ae2 system
which mostly manages on demand craftings
the patterns for the stuff we use in huge amounts have all been multiplied a lot
and instead of using interfaces
we input materials directly inside the machines with the embedded crafting buffers
those are blocks that can be used when building the mid to late game multi blocks
and when we craft huge amounts of early game materials
we can see that the main limitation is integer 32
and that we can process those amounts of items in a single tick
also you can now guess how we ended up needing 8 exabyte storage crafting units
this was our main ae2 network
but not the only one
we have countless sub networks for all kinds of purposes
such as assembly lines of all kinds
but we also have another huge and spread network
the mass produced storage one
this one will manage all of the resources produced and processed in unlimited amounts
and it still uses digital singularity cells
most of our raw resources come from this eye of harmony
with its 211 astral array fabricators
it works with a 16000 parallel multiplier
and it will produce about anything we could need
the biggest exception is probably a orundum
this material is a weird thing
that could be produced by fusing together two plates
but we are getting it as an ore from a space elevator
from a space elevator
we are also pumping all kinds of fluids which we could need
also we still have some void miners in the deep dark
just to integrate with any possible ore that can be seen in NEI
the ones we care about are processed in integrated ore facilities
while the rest is stocked up in yet another subnetwork
to power all of that stuff
we are using the shielded Lagrangian annihilation matrix
to fuel it
we use antimatter
five millions at a time
which will output energy in bursts of almost integer 64 energy units at a time
we store that energy in a wireless energy network
which has a really huge capacity
our generator to run uses antimatter as fuel
to produce such fuel
we use 24 semi stable antimatter stabilization sequencers
and this is a multi block with some peculiar requirements
the most important thing to know is that it needs the same amount of antimatter in each hatch
and that it will keep randomly changing the value in its hatches
to keep it under check
we use SFM and a bunch of covers
and the production will also use some quite expensive materials
to make a decent amount of antimatter
to boost the production
we also had to make a dedicated naquadah fuel production facility
all done with AE2 hatches and sub networks to reach high enough crafting speeds
for power generation
we also have 100 Dyson Spheres
but those are no longer loaded
since the power production is negligible
and now we can step outside
and start having a look at the machines in our base
starting from the light bulb on top of our main building
the forge of the gods
that huge thing is used to work materials at high temperatures
the main structure can host 4 different modules
that can do different kind of tasks
the first one is just a better blast furnace
the second one acts more like a blast smelter
melting materials down to liquid form
the real advantage here is that we no longer need vacuum freezer
the third module can turn any element into plasma
this will offer alternatives to fusion recipes
and often reduce the amount of needed steps
and we can also use it to make plasmas that fusion can't make
the last module can only make two recipes
magmatter and quark gluon
and the reason NEI looks weird on those two crafting recipes is because
this is a really particular processing mechanic
to make magmatter
machine will start by giving us 2 fluids
we have to calculate the difference
multiply it by 144
and give it back as plasma of the material of a tiny dust the machine also gave us
for the quark gluon
we start with some random elements
and we have to send back plasma equivalent to 9 times what the machine gave us
the working speed and efficiency of all of those modules can scale up with the upgrades
that we can unlock in a skill tree inside the main controller of the structure
those skills are unlocked by using Graviton Shards
points that are earned by reaching milestones in the usage of the machine
and this is not the only place where we have to face automation minigames
the other complex tasks are given by the waterline
here we have an 8 step process for filtering water
but let's see those steps one at a time
the first step is a clarifier
which will simply use filters to remove the big particles suspended in our dirty water
the second step is ozonation
we inject some ozone in the water
to take out some of the contaminants that react with it
the only challenge here is to pick the right size of input hatch
and keep it filled up
the next step is flocculation
which consists of adding some flocculant to aggregate
and then collect suspended particulates
and here things starts to get interesting
because we have to insert the flocculant in perfect multiplies for it to work properly
but it's not too hard
we can ensure the insertion of a perfect amount with a bunch of covers
next we have to correct the acidity of our water in a pH neutralization plant
here we will be adding some alkaline or acid stuff to correct the pH
to automate that process
we can use the embedded pH sensors
and some basic Redstone control
once we neutralize the pH of our water
we have to do some Thermal cycles
to ensure no weird stuff is left inside it
to do so, we blast it with helium plasma above the temperature of the sun
and then cool it down to absolute 0
here, to keep the temperature in check we use SFM
with an external dummy item to keep track of the heat cycles
that will leave some ions in the water
so
we have to use laser to shoot those out of our water
but we have to do that with different lenses
in the correct order and with the correct timing
luckily
we have a sensor that will make swaps easy
next we have the decontaminant degasser unit
which will have random made up issues
just to add an extra challenge
this machine can't express its feelings properly
the best it can do is try to communicate with us in binary
so we hired another SFM controller to talk with her
finally
we have the Absolute Baryonic Perfection Purification unit
that machine will fix every subatomic particle out of position contained in our water
to automate this
we have built a setup
that will first prepare some quark releasing catalysts in a specific order
and then one by one insert those inside the machine
but our Redstone and automation challenges aren't done yet
we also had to manage black holes
this machine is mostly a powerful compressor
but there are some recipes that require a strength that only a black hole can achieve
to make this machine work
we first have to open a black hole inside it with a black hole seed
however this black hole will slowly shrink
becoming less and less stable
to halt that process
we can add some space time to the machine
but the cost of space time will keep increasing exponentially
and when the black hole is at its most unstable phase
it will manage to compress four times as many items at once
and when the upkeep cost becomes too high
we can close the black hole with a collapsar
to properly manage all the different recipes we are going to do
and the correct insertion of the items
we have designed a proper Redstone circuit
we have 2 different ones with different timer settings
and we also have two extra black hole compressors
to passively make eternal singularities
next we can check out the assembly lines
the oldest 14 are for generic craftings
here we do all the recipes we need in small amounts
the data sticks with the unlocked recipes are kept in chained data banks that are connected by optical fibers
and here we have a collection of stuff we almost never craft
and thus got removed even from this set of assembly lines
on the contrary
stuff we need often but is really hard to craft
is made in the nearby advanced assembly lines
here we use way more energy
and we craft small batches of expensive stuff
and even with all of those overclocks
it still takes a while to craft those time intense parts
to manage the parallelization of the assembly line
we have a slightly more complex item feeding system
which has an AE2 subnetwork for each slice of each assembly line
overclocking isn't efficient
so for stuff that doesn't take as much time
and we need in bigger amounts
we have a different setup
we have 8 lines of 8 assembly lines
with each line sharing the same inputs
and those are almost always constantly crafting lots of things
but there was one thing which we needed in way bigger amounts
that this setup wouldn't keep up with
circuits
for those
we made 88 assembly lines sharing the same inputs
but even that still wasn't enough
the storage for our queued up craftings were constantly full
so we started making extra building
dedicated to each circuit
the next thing that caused some inventory management issues
were our dimensionally transcendent plasma forges
we have 60 of those
36 of those are working on demand crafting
provided by the crafting buffer Linked In our base
the other 24 are passively doing stuff using the convergence module
which otherwise we wouldn't be able to keep up with
finally
there are many machines we had to build in huge amounts
to keep up with the processing demands
most of those don't have any particularly hard mechanic to showcase
so I think we can just fly around and have a look
if you want to have a look by yourself
and inspect anything you want
you can download the save in the video description
next to the spawn
you should be able to find a chest
with all of my equipment
if you want the mini map to be complete
I also included journey map files
once you are ready
you can use the relocator to relocate to the base
now
before you do anything
there are a couple of things you should know and check
the Wireless Energy battery is linked to a player
I don't know how it works in single player
but I assume you'd still have to join my network if you wanted to use Wireless Energy for any modification you could want to try
if the Questbook command doesn't work
you can just rebuild the controller of the main power generator
just make sure it now has your name
and to turn on wireless mode
one other thing you might won't be able to use is ae2
in that case
rebuild the security terminal
and then relink the wireless terminal
next
sometimes while loading backups
the waterline could stop working
in that case
just turn on the main controller
other times the forge automations will get stuck
if that is the case
remove the fluids from the afflicted setup
and reset the mini game
this rarely happens
so make sure it is stuck before being the cause of the issue
I probably forgot other things
just ask in the comments
bye bye
欢迎回来
我们的旅程已经结束
我想我们可以好好总结一下这次冒险
我们的整个基地位于一个自给自足的维度
这里没有雨
怪物不会生成
永远是白天
我们在造出第一枚火箭时得到了这个私人维度奖励
这里是大楼的主厅
位于基地的中间
这有一个屏幕
它会展示主电池的电量
有一些终端用于监视燃料的数量
以及一些大后期材料
至于存储和自动合成的设备
我们的主AE控制器位于上方
为了以更简单的方式管理频道
我们使用了p2p和无线连接器的紧密组合
把所有控制器都映射到一堵漂亮的墙上
我们可以使用网络可视化工具查看所有频道
但它对我们在这里工作用处不大
这里还有所有的合成CPU
我们有不同尺寸的
但最大的是那些配备了奇点合成存储器的
这些可以容纳高达8EB的订单
虽然我们永远不会接近那个数量
但它们在下大订单时很有帮助
否则将需要太大的传统CPU
所有这些CPU也在做一些自动发起的订单
这些不是来自合成卡或发信器
而是来自库存维持器
这些能很容易维持我们想要的库存数量
当有需要时，它会发起具有特定大小的订单
接下来是我们的主要通用存储
为了管理所有的东西
我们最终使用了人造宇宙存储单元
但这只是我们的主网
主要用于一些按需制作
我们大量使用的东西的样板倍增了好几次
不同于使用ME接口
我们直接用有带缓存的样板总成向机器内输入材料
这些是在中后期多方块机器中使用的方块
当我们制作大量早期游戏材料时
我们可以看到主要限制是int32
我们可以在一个游戏刻内处理这些数量的物品
你现在应该可以猜到为什么要8EB的存储制作单元
这是我们的主网
但不是唯一的一个
我们有无数各种用途的子网
比如各种装配线
但我们还有另一个庞大而分散的网络
用于存储批量生产的物品
它将管理无限量生产和加工的所有资源
它仍然使用数字奇点单元
我们大部分的原始资源来自鸿蒙之眼
EoH中塞了211个星阵
也就是16000倍并行
它会生产出我们需要的任何东西
最大的例外可能是合成玉
这是一种奇怪的材料
可以通过将两个板压缩在一起产生
但我们是从太空电梯里获取它的矿石的
从太空电梯里
我们还抽取了可能需要的各种液体
另外，我们还有一些位于漆黑世界的虚空采矿厂
为了补充任何可能在NEI中看到的矿物
我们关心的矿物在集成矿石处理厂中加工
其余的储存在另一个子网中
为所有这些东西供电
我们用的是屏蔽拉格朗日湮灭矩阵
为了给它供给燃料
我们使用反物质
一次五百万升
它将一次输出接近2^63 EU
我们将能量存储在无线电网中
它的容量非常大
我们的发电机使用反物质作为燃料
要生产这种燃料
我们使用24个半稳定反物质稳定序列器
这是一个有一些特殊要求的多方块
最重要的是每个仓室需要有等量的反物质
它会不断随机改变仓室中的反物质数量
为了保持数量一致
我们使用SFM和一堆覆盖板
发电过程也会使用一些相当昂贵的材料
制造大量的反物质
为了提高产量
我们还必须建造一个专门的硅岩燃料生产设施
所有这些都是通过AE仓室和子网完成的
以达到足够高的制造速度
对于发电
我们还有100个戴森球
但那些区块不再加载了
因为它们产出的电力微不足道
现在我们可以出去
看看我们基地里的机器
从我们主楼顶上的灯泡开始
也就是诸神之锻炉
那个巨大的东西是用来在高温下处理材料的
主体结构可以承载4个不同的模块
用于处理不同类型的任务
第一个只是一个更好的高炉
第二个更像是熔液高炉
能够将材料熔化成液态
真正的优势是我们不再需要真空冷冻
第三个模块可以将任何元素转化为等离子体
这将提供聚变配方的替代
并经常减少所需步骤的数量
我们也可以用它制造无法聚变的等离子体
最后一个模块只能做两个配方
磁物质和夸克胶子等离子体
在NEI的这两个上看起来很奇怪的原因是因为
它拥有一种非常特殊的加工机制
要制造磁物质
机器将从给我们两种液体开始
我们必须计算它们的差
乘以144
把机器给我们的小搓粉对应的等离子体输入回机器
对于夸克胶子等离子体
我们从一些随机元素开始
我们必须送回机器给我们的9倍的等离子体
所有这些模块的工作速度和效率都可以随着升级而提高
我们可以在结构的主方块内的技能树中解锁它们
这些技能通过使用引力子碎片解锁
那是通过达到机器使用里程碑而获得的积分
这不是我们唯一要面对的自动化小游戏
其他复杂的任务来自净化水线
这里我们有一个过滤水的8步过程
让我们一步步来看
第一步是澄清
它将简单地使用过滤器来去除悬浮在脏水中的大颗粒
第二步是臭氧化
我们在水中注入一些臭氧
去除一些与之反应的污染物
这里唯一的挑战是选择合适尺寸的输入仓
并保持它充满
下一步是絮凝
它包括添加一些絮凝剂用于絮凝
然后收集悬浮微粒
现在事情开始变得有趣起来
因为我们必须以完美的倍数输入絮凝剂才能正常工作
但这并不太难
我们可以用一堆覆盖板确保输入完美的数量
接下来，我们在pH中和装置中校正水的酸度
在这里，我们将添加一些碱性或酸性的东西来校正pH值
要自动化该过程
我们可以使用嵌入式pH传感器
和一些基本的红石电路
一旦我们中和了水的酸碱度
我们必须做一些热循环
以确保水里没有奇怪的东西
为此，我们用高于太阳温度的氦等离子体加热它
然后将其冷却到绝对零度
在这里，为了控制温度，我们使用SFM
使用外部虚拟物品以跟踪热量循环
这会在水中留下一些离子
所以
我们必须用激光把它们从水里射出来
但是我们必须用不同的棱镜来做
同时要保证正确的顺序和时间
幸运的是
我们有一个传感器可以让交换变得轻松
接下来是净化脱气装置
这将有随机编造的问题
只是为了增加一个额外的挑战
这台机器不能正确地表达它的感情
它最多只能用二进制和我们交流
所以我们雇了另一个SFM管理员和她谈谈
最后
是绝对重子完美净化单元
那台机器会修复水里每一个处于错误位置的亚原子粒子
要自动化这个过程
我们搭好一个装置
首先按照特定顺序准备一些夸克释放催化剂
然后一个接一个地将它们输入机器
但是我们的红石和自动化挑战还没有结束
我们还必须管理黑洞
这台机器主要是一台强大的压缩机
但是有些配方需要只有黑洞才能达到的强度
为了让这台机器工作
我们首先得用黑洞种子在里面打开一个黑洞
然而这个黑洞会慢慢缩小
变得越来越不稳定
要停止这个过程
我们可以给机器增加一些时空
但时空成本将呈指数增长
当黑洞处于最不稳定的阶段时
它将一次压缩四倍多的物品
当维护成本过高时
我们可以用黑洞坍塌器关闭黑洞
为了正确管理我们要做的所有不同配方
以及正确输入物品
我们设计了一个合适的红石电路
我们有两套不同的定时器设置
还有两个额外的黑洞压缩机
用于被动制造永恒奇点
接下来我们可以去看看装配线
最老的14个用于通用配方
我们在这些装配线上运行只有少量需求的配方
具有解锁配方的闪存保存在通过光纤串联的数据库中
这里我们收集了一些几乎从未制作过的东西
因此从这组装配线上被移除了
另一方面
我们经常需要但很难制作的东西
是在附近的进阶装配线上制造的
在这里我们使用更多的能量
我们小批量制作昂贵的东西
即使有这么多超频
制作那些耗时长的部件仍然需要一段时间
为了实现装配线的并行
我们有一个稍微复杂一点的物品供给系统
每个装配线的每个切片都有一个子网
超频效率不高
所以对于不需要太多时间
同时需要更大数量的
我们有不同的设置
我们有8*8条装配线
每一行共享相同的输入
这些几乎总是在不断地制作很多东西
但是有一样东西我们需要更多
而这个设置的速度跟不上
就是电路板
对于那些
我们建造了共享相同的输入的88条装配线
但这还不够
用于缓存原料的储存总是爆满
所以我们开始建造额外的建筑
用于制造各类电路
下一个导致一些库存管理问题的东西
是超维度等离子锻炉
我们有60个锻炉
其中36个按需制作
由连接到基地的输入总成提供原材料
其他24个正在使用超维校准矩阵进行被动生产
否则我们跟不上需求
最后
我们必须大量制造许多机器
来满足材料处理需求
大多数都没有什么特别难的机制可以展示
所以我想我们可以飞过去看看
如果你想自己看看
并检查任何想要的东西
你可以下载简介里的存档
在出生点旁边
你应该能找到一个箱子
里面有我所有的装备
如果你想要完整的地图
我还在压缩包里加入地图文件
一旦你准备好了
你可以使用定位器传送到基地
现在
在你做任何事情之前
有几件事你应该知道并检查
无线电网与玩家绑定
我不知道单人模式该怎么处理
但我假设如果你想使用无线电网
你仍然需要加入我的网络
如果任务书提到的命令不起作用
你可以重建主发电机的控制器
只要确保它现在有你的名字
并打开无线模式
你可能无法使用的另一个东西是AE
那样的话
重建安全终端
然后重新连接无线终端
下一个
有时在加载备份时
净化水线可能会停止工作
那样的话
只需打开主控制器
有的时候神锻自动化会卡住
如果是这样的话
清除受影响的装置中的液体
并重置小游戏
这种情况很少发生
所以要确保它卡住了
否则你可能变成它卡住的原因
我可能忘了其他事
就在评论里问问
拜拜
（gt  global_energy_join  your_name  __tomm__
把your_name改成你的游戏id）